Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XLI is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XLII is arranged in 4 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XLIII is arranged in 3 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XLI. RAILWAY LABOR ACT
  - Sub-Series 282-4. Railway Labor Act
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 467, Folder 1)
      May 26, 1950-June 8, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 467, Folder 2)
      May 18-25, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 467, Folder 3)
      May 11-17, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 467, Folder 4)
      May 1-10, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1949-1950 (Box 467, Folder 5)
      November 1949-April 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1952 (Box 467, Folder 6)
      January-February 1952.
    - Union Shop, 1948-1949 (Box 467, Folder 7)
      1948-October 1949.
    - Union Shop, 1951 (Box 467, Folder 8)
      March 6, 1951-December 31, 1951.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 467, Folder 9)
      November 1-8, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 467, Folder 10)
      October 18-31, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 467, Folder 11)
      October 1-17, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 1)
      September 21-30, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 2)
      September 14-20, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 3)
      September 9-13, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 4)
      September 6-8, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 5)
      September 2-5, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 6)
      August 31, 1950-September 1, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 7)
      August 28-30, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 8)
      August 20-27, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 9)
      August 12-, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 10)
      1950 August 11
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 11)
      August 3-10, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 12)
      July 26, 1950-August 2, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 13)
      July 19-25, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 14)
      July 14-18, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 15)
      July 11-13, 1950.
    - Union Shop, 1950 (Box 468, Folder 16)
      July 6-10, 1950.
- Series XLII. CREDENTIALS
  - Sub-Series 285-4. Credentials
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and General Representatives, 1933-1959 (Box 469, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 285-5. Credentials
    - Chairmen, State Legislative Committees, 1950-1957 (Box 469, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 285-6. Credentials
    - Legislative Representatives, 1955-1957 (Box 469, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 285-7. Credentials
    - Grand Lodge Staff, 1955 (Box 469, Folder 4)
- Series XLIII. EXPENSE ACCOUNTS
  - Sub-Series 286-0. Expense Accounts
    - General, 1965 (Box 469, Folder 5)
    - General, 1961-1964 (Box 469, Folder 6)
      May 1961-64.
    - General, 1955-1961 (Box 469, Folder 7)
      1955-April 1961.
    - General, 1953-1954 (Box 469, Folder 8)
      July 1953-December 1954.
    - General, 1950-1953 (Box 469, Folder 9)
      1950-June 1953.
    - General, 1946-1949 (Box 469, Folder 10)
    - General, 1931-1945 (Box 469, Folder 11)
    - General, 1923-1930 (Box 469, Folder 12)
    - General, 1921-1924 (Box 469, Folder 13)
    - General, 1931 (Box 469, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 286-1. Expense Accounts
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1963-1964 (Box 469, Folder 15)
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1957-1962 (Box 469, Folder 16)
      June 1957-62.
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1951-1957 (Box 469, Folder 17)
      1951-May 1957.
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1943-1950 (Box 469, Folder 18)
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1933-1942 (Box 470, Folder 1)
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1924-1925 (Box 470, Folder 2)
    - Vice Grand Presidents. Chapman, H.J., 1933-1935 (Box 470, Folder 3)
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1932 (Box 470, Folder 4)
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1931 (Box 470, Folder 5)
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1930 (Box 470, Folder 6)
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1926-1929 (Box 470, Folder 7)
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1926-1935 (Box 470, Folder 8)
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1922-1923 (Box 470, Folder 9)
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1921-1922 (Box 470, Folder 10)
    - Vice Grand Presidents, 1921 (Box 470, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 286-2. Expense Accounts
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Robinson, C.E., 1965 (Box 470, Folder 12)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Clark, J.O., 1958-1960 (Box 470, Folder 13)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Reynolds, F.V., 1958-1967 (Box 470, Folder 14)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Ulrich, H.D., 1961 (Box 470, Folder 15)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Robertson, C.N., 1964 (Box 470, Folder 16)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Dunaway, H.P., 1960-1961 (Box 470, Folder 17)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Crawford, W.M., 1958-1961 (Box 470, Folder 18)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. McCauley, A., 1961 (Box 470, Folder 19)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Murphy, W.B., 1958-1959 (Box 470, Folder 20)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Gibson, G.W., 1958-1963 (Box 470, Folder 21)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Mose, A., 1958-1963 (Box 470, Folder 22)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Barber, H., 1959-1960 (Box 470, Folder 23)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Schmidt, H.P., 1960 (Box 470, Folder 24)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Ripp, H.J., 1960 (Box 470, Folder 25)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Giroux, C.A., 1958-1962 (Box 470, Folder 26)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Kelly, E.F., 1958-1961 (Box 470, Folder 27)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Grimes, T.D., 1958 (Box 470, Folder 28)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. General; Babcock, R.A.; Barber, H.; Bruen, F.; Campbell, D.K.; Clancy, P.T.; Clark, J.O.; Courtney, E.; Crawford, W.M., 1937-1957 (Box 470, Folder 29)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Davie, A.R., 1965 (Box 470, Folder 30)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Erickson, L.M., 1958-1962 (Box 470, Folder 31)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Day, P.F.; Dickinson, W.J.; Erickson, L.M.; Gibson, G.W.; Giroux, C.A.; Goodwin, H.L., 1940-1957 (Box 470, Folder 32)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Lanza, E.A., 1957-1966 (Box 471, Folder 1)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Grimes, T.D.; Harrison, H.C.; Kelly, E.F.; Lanza, E.A., 1938-1957 (Box 471, Folder 2)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Mayberry, R.M.; Mose, A,; Murphy, W.B.; McCarthy, F.E.; McCarthy, R.J.; McKinney, L., 1938-1957 (Box 471, Folder 3)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Reynolds, F.V.; Roers, E.L.; Sommerfield, C.F.; Summerville, F.J.; Sylvester, L.H., 1937-1957 (Box 471, Folder 4)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Sylvester, L.H., 1958 (Box 471, Folder 5)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Tait, W.A.; Turner, W.J.; Tuttle, H.L.; Wilson, E.J., 1936-1957 (Box 471, Folder 6)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Williams, G., 1960-1961 (Box 471, Folder 7)